<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<resources>
  <string name="sound_enhance_strings_aptx_playback_quality_detail_txt">[Ţĥé åûðîö ḿåý šķîþ öŕ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ðîšçöññéçţéð ðûé ţö ñéţŵöŕķ îñţéŕƒéŕéñçé šîñçé ţĥé βļûéţööţĥ çöññéçţîöñ åñð ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ûšé šåḿé ƒŕéQûéñçý ɓåñð (2.4ĜĤž).

Ţö ĝéţ å šţåɓļé çöññéçţîöñ, ţŕý ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šöļûţîöñš:
・ Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ
・ ḾöVé ţö ŵĥéŕé ţĥéŕé îš ñö öţĥéŕ ñéţŵöŕķ ðéVîçé ûšîñĝ 2.4ĜĤž ɓåñð
・ Šéļéçţ [åþţ×] one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="sound_enhance_strings_ldac_playback_quality_detail_txt">[Ţĥé åûðîö ḿåý šķîþ öŕ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ðîšçöññéçţéð ðûé ţö ñéţŵöŕķ îñţéŕƒéŕéñçé šîñçé ţĥé βļûéţööţĥ çöññéçţîöñ åñð ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ûšé šåḿé ƒŕéQûéñçý ɓåñð (2.4ĜĤž).

Ţö ĝéţ å šţåɓļé çöññéçţîöñ, ţŕý ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šöļûţîöñš:
・ Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ
・ ḾöVé ţö ŵĥéŕé ţĥéŕé îš ñö öţĥéŕ ñéţŵöŕķ ðéVîçé ûšîñĝ 2.4ĜĤž ɓåñð
・ Šéļéçţ [βéšţ éƒƒöŕţ]

Îƒ ýöû ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö ķééþ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ, šéļéçţ [βéšţ éƒƒöŕţ].
Ţĥé åûðîö îš þļåýéð åţ ţĥé ḿöšţ åþþŕöþŕîåţé ɓîţ ŕåţé ðéþéñðîñĝ öñ ñéţŵöŕķ éñVîŕöñḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four]</string>
  <string name="sound_enhance_strings_wireless_playback_quality_aptx_desc_txt">[Ýöû çåñ šéļéçţ ţĥé çöðéç ƒöŕ ûšé ŵĥéñ çöññéçţéð ţö ţĥé åþţ× ĤÐ ðéVîçé. Îƒ ţĥé åûðîö šķîþš öŕ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ îš îñţéŕŕûþţéð, ţåþ [»%s«] ţö ļéåŕñ ĥöŵ ţö éšţåɓļîšĥ šţåɓļé çöññéçţîöñ ɓéţŵééñ ţĥé ðéVîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]</string>
  <string name="sound_enhance_strings_wireless_playback_quality_desc_txt">[Ýöû çåñ éñĵöý Ĥî-Ŕéš Åûðîö ɓý çöññéçţîñĝ åñ ĻÐÅÇ ðéVîçé Vîå βļûéţööţĥ çöññéçţîöñ. Îƒ ţĥé åûðîö šķîþš öŕ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ îš îñţéŕŕûþţéð, ţåþ [»%s«] ţö ļéåŕñ ĥöŵ ţö éšţåɓļîšĥ šţåɓļé çöññéçţîöñ ɓéţŵééñ ţĥé ðéVîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="sound_enhance_strings_wireless_playback_quality_detail_txt">[Ţĥé åûðîö ḿåý šķîþ öŕ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ðîšçöññéçţéð ðûé ţö ñéţŵöŕķ îñţéŕƒéŕéñçé šîñçé ţĥé βļûéţööţĥ çöññéçţîöñ åñð ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ûšé šåḿé ƒŕéQûéñçý ɓåñð (2.4ĜĤž).

Föŕ šţåɓļé çöññéçţîöñ, ţŕý ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šöļûţîöñš:
<li><ul>Ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ Öƒƒ
<li>ḾöVé ţö ţĥé þļåçé ŵĥéŕé ţĥéŕé îš ñö öţĥéŕ ñéţŵöŕķ ðéVîçéš ûšîñĝ 2.4ĜĤž ɓåñð</li>
<li>Šéļéçţ [Çöññéçţîöñ þŕéƒéŕŕéð]</li></ul>

Îƒ ýöû ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö ķééþ ţĥé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç Vîå ŴĻÅÑ, šéļéçţ [Çöññéçţîöñ þŕéƒéŕŕéð].</li> one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
</resources>